You can keep it now too
You also told me not to sleep back then
Yeah
I'll keep that in mind then
I won't lose it this time
Su Mingyao why didn't you tell me earlier
I didn't know how to say it
You could have told me at the wedding banquet
You could have said it the day of the fashion line release
But I didn't want to say it like that
I could prove I was the one who signed it
And prove that the old item
Has always been in my box
But I didn't want to put myself
In the position of your savior
I didn't want you to choose me out of gratitude
If you treat me well
I hope it's because you want to
Not because you feel you owe me
Su Mengyao
I'm treating you well now